Guide to the Pittsburgh Playhouse School of the Theater Records, 1934-1994 CTC.1981.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs and Negatives, 1935-1993; III.
  - Photo Albums, 1946-1964; 4.
    - Album 5, 1961-1964 (Box 115, Portfolio 5)
      - Take Her She's Mine, 1963; 32.
      - West Side Story, 1964; 33.
      - Sunday in New York, 1964; 34.
      - Do You Know the Milky Way, 1964; 35.
      - The Tenth Man, 1964; 36.
      - Calculated Risk, 1964; 37.
      - Wish You Were Here, 1964; 38.
      - Oh Dad Poor Dad..., 1964; 39.
      - Naughty Nifties, 1964; 40.
      - Twelfth Night, 1964; 41.
      - Enter Laughing, 1964; 42.
      - Snow Queen and the Goblin, 1963; 43.
      - Alice in Wonderland, 1964; 44.
      - Rumpelstiltskin, 1964; 45.
- Programs, 1934-1994; IV.
  Within this series are programs of full-scale Playhouse productions, school or student, Playhouse Jr., special events, Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre, and Dance. They are arranged in chronological order by season.
  - 1934-1935 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Art and Mrs. Bottle, 1.
    - Children of Darkness, 2.
    - No More Ladies, 3.
    - Spread Eagle, 4.
    - He Who Gets Slapped, 5.
  - 1935-1936 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - The Wind and The Rain, 1.
    - The Constant Wife, 2.
    - Pelleas and Melisande, 3.
    - On The Spot, 4.
    - From Morn to Midnight, 5.
    - Springtime for Henry, 6.
  - 1936-1937 (Box 116, Folder 3-4)
    - Russet Mantle, 1.
    - Streets of New York, 2.
    - Scarlet Letter, 3.
    - Laburnum Grove, 4.
    - The First Legion, 5.
    - In a Garden, 6.
  - 1937-1938 (Box 116, Folder 5-6)
    - Hold Your Hats, 1.
    - Pursuit of Happiness, 2.
    - Excursion, 3.
    - The Spider, 4.
    - Accent on Youth, 5.
    - Libel, 6.
    - Autumn Crocus, 7.
  - 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 7-8)
    - It Can't Happen Here, 1.
    - And Niobe Wept, 2.
    - Personal Appearance, 3.
    - Night Must Fall, 4.
    - Tonight at 8:30, 5.
    - The Doctor in Spite of Himself/The Hypochondriac, 6.
    - Meet My Sister, 7.
  - 1939-1940 (Box 117, Folder 1-2)
    - Private Lives, 1.
    - I Want a Policeman, 2.
    - Thank Your Stars, 3.
    - Ghost of Yankee Doodle, 4.
    - Private Lives, 5.
    - Biography, 6.
    - The Road to Rome, 7.
    - Our Town, 8.
  - 1940-1941 (Box 117, Folder 3-4)
    - Reflected Glory, 1.
    - See My Lawyer, 2.
    - Gas Light, 3.
    - Here Today, 4.
    - Lend an Ear, 5.
    - Stage Door, 6.
    - 15th Amateur Players Contest, 7.
    - Morning's at Seven, 8.
    - Green Pastures, 9.
  - 1941-1942 (Box 117, Folder 5-6)
    - Out of the Frying Pan, 1.
    - Charley's Aunt, 2.
    - Mr. Mrs. North, 3.
    - The Male Animal, 4.
    - Flight to the West, 5.
    - Flora Robson in Suspect, 6.
    - Dots Dash, 7.
    - Green Grow the Lilacs, 8.
  - 1942-1943 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Goodbye Again, 1.
    - Cradle Song, 2.
    - Mrs. Moonlight, 3.
    - Count Your Blessings, 4.
    - The Eve of St. Mark, 5.
    - George Washington Slept Here, 6.
    - Ten Minute Alibi, 7.
    - Yes My Darling Daughter, 8.
  - Summer 1943 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Penny Wise, 1.
    - A Murder has Been Arranged, 2.
    - Old Acquaintance, 3.
    - The Vinegar Tree, 4.
    - The Night of January 16th, 5.
  - 1943-1944 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Petticoat Fever, 1.
    - Blind Alley, 2.
    - On Borrowed Time, 3.
    - Candida, 4.
    - Skylark, 5.
    - Everybody is Wonderful, 6.
    - Post Road, 7.
    - Sun-up, 8.
  - Summer 1944 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Heaven Can Wait, 1.
    - Nine Girls, 2.
    - The Bishop Misbehaves, 3.
    - The Play's the Thing, 4.
  - 1944-1945 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1.
    - Papa is All, 2.
    - Darkling Plain, 3.
    - Dame Nature, 4.
    - They Walk Alone, 5.
    - The Damask Cheek, 6.
    - The Great Big Step, 7.
    - A Party
  - 1945-1946 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Small Miracle, 1.
    - Blithe Spirit, 2.
    - Hand In Glove, 3.
    - Fashion, 4.
    - The Little Foxes, 5.
    - Kiss and Tell, 6.
    - Soldier's Wife, 7.
    - The Front Page, 8.
  - 1946-1947 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Both Your Houses, 1.
    - Boy Meets Girl, 2.
    - Juno and the Paycock, 3.
    - The Poor Nut, 4.
    - The Lady of Leley Square, 5.
    - Macbeth, 6.
    - The Hasty Heart, 7.
    - After Hours, 8.
  - 1947-1948 (Box 117, Folder 14-15)
    - Dream Girl, 1.
    - June Moon, 2.
    - Another Part of the Forest, 3.
    - The Late George Apley, 4.
    - The Sound of Hunting, 5.
    - All My Sons, 6.
    - The Girl From Wyoming, 7.
    - Years Ago, 8.
  - 1948-1949 (Box 117, Folder 16-17)
    - Joan of Lorraine, 1.
    - Shorty, 2.
    - She Loves Me Not, 3.
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, 4.
    - Command Decision, 5.
    - Anna Christie, 6.
    - Of All Things, 7.
    - Remember Me, 8.
  - 1949-1950 (Box 117, Folder 18-19)
    - The Traitor, 1.
    - This Is My Valley, 2.
    - Strange Bedfellows, 3.
    - Grand Guignol, 4.
    - Captain Brassbound's Conversion, 5.
    - Two Blind Mice, 6.
    - Fifty Grand, 7.
    - Jenny Kissed Me, 8.
  - 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 1-2)
    - The Wedding, 1.
    - The Velvet Glove, 2.
    - On Your Mark, 3.
    - Arsenic and Old Lace, 4.
    - Goodbye My Fancy, 5.
    - At War With the Army, 6.
    - The Charm Kid, 7.
    - Detective Story, 8.
  - 1951-1952 (Box 118, Folder 3-4)
    - The Curious Savage, 1.
    - Water Witch, 2.
    - Present Laughter, 3.
    - Twentieth Century, 4.
    - Peg O' My Heart, 5.
    - The Voice of the Turtle, 6.
    - Wonderful Good, 7.
    - The Happy Time, 8.
  - 1952-1953 (Box 118, Folder 5-7)
    - Ah Wilderness!, 1.
    - Remains To Be Seen, 2.
    - Dance for Joy, 3.
    - The Holly and the Ivy, 4.
    - Three Men on a Horse, 5.
    - The White Steed, 6.
    - The Best Foot Forward, 7.
    - The Royal Family, 8.
    - Life With Mother, 9.
    - Three To One, 10.
    - Payment Deferred, 11.
    - The Little Wife, 12.
  - 1953-1954 (Box 118, Folder 8-10)
    - Mister Roberts, 1.
    - John Loves Mary, 2.
    - Two on an Island, 3.
    - Affairs of State, 4.
    - A Kiss for Cinderella, 5.
    - The Time of the Cuckoo, 6.
    - Take a Giant Step, 7.
    - The Queen's Husband, 8.
    - Happy Birthday, 9.
    - Home of the Brave, 10.
    - Between Friends, 11.
    - See How They Run, 12.
    - The Ghost of Mr. Penny, 13.
  - 1954-1955 (Box 118, Folder 11-13)
    - My Three Angels, 1.
    - Pygmalion, 2.
    - Of Mice and Men, 3.
    - White Sheep of the Family, 4.
    - Sabrina Fair, 5.
    - Girl on the Via Flaminia, 6.
    - The Women, 7.
    - The Late Christopher Bean, 8.
    - The Crucible, 9.
    - The Little Hut, 10.
    - The Lighter Side, 11.
    - The Caine Court Mutiny, 12.
    - The King of Hearts, 13.
  - 1955-1956 (Box 118, Folder 14-16)
    - Dial M for Murder, 1.
    - Reclining Figure, 2.
    - The Remarkable Mr. Pennypacker, 3.
    - Our Town, 4.
    - Accounting for Love, 5.
    - Among Ourselves, 6.
    - The Jest, 7.
    - Oh Men! Oh Women!, 8.
    - Morning's at Seven, 9.
    - The Torchbearers, 10.
    - Roomful of Roses, 11.
    - What's the Rush?, 12.
    - Champagne Complex, 13.
    - Solid Gold Cadillac, 14.
    - Puss in Boots, 15.
  - 1956-1957 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Bus Stop, 1.
    - Anniversary Waltz, 2.
    - Desperate Hours, 3.
    - Teach Me How to Cry, 4.
    - The Mousetrap, 5.
    - The Man From Home, 6.
  - 1956-1957 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Love from Judy, 1.
    - Loud Red Patrick, 2.
    - View From the Bridge, 3.
    - Teahouse of the August Moon, 4.
    - Witness for the Prosecution, 5.
    - Off the Top, 6.
    - Ali Baba and the 40 Thieves, 7.
    - Greensleeves' Magic, 8.
    - Snow Queen and the Goblin, 9.
    - Arthur and the Magic Sword, 10.
  - 1957-1958 (Box 119, Folder 2-4)
    - The Boyfriend, 1.
    - The Potting Shed, 2.
    - Smilin' Through, 3.
    - Speaking of Murder, 4.
    - Finian's Rainbow, 5.
    - Summer and Smoke, 6.
    - Holiday for Lovers, 7.
    - The Matchmaker, 8.
    - Mr. Ambassador, 9.
    - Tongue in Cheek, 10.
    - Separate Tables, 11.
    - Bernardine, 12.
    - Marco and the Thieves, 13.
    - Cinderella, 14.
    - Hansel and Gretel, 15.
    - Magic Horn, 16.
    - The Seven Year Itch, 17.
    - Sinbad the Sailor, 18.
  - 1958-1959 (Box 119, Folder 5-7)
    - No Time for Sergeants, 1.
    - Lost in the Stars, 2.
    - Skin of Our Teeth, 3.
    - A Visit to a Small Planet, 4.
    - King Midas and the Golden Touch, 5.
    - Pinocchio, 6.
    - Beauty and the Beast, 7.
    - Blue Denim, 8.
    - Sleeping Beauty, 9.
    - Mary Stuart, 10.
    - Tree Grows in Brooklyn, 11.
    - A Hole In the Head, 12.
    - The Cave Dwellers, 13.
    - The Rope Dancers, 14.
    - To the Point, 15.
    - Middle of the Night, 16.
    - Tunnel of Love, 17.
    - The Man in the Dog Suit, 18.
    - The Chairs / The Bald Soprano, 19.
  - 1959-1960 (Box 119, Folder 8-10)
    - Once More With Feeling, 1.
    - Who Was That Lady I Saw You With?, 2.
    - Epitaph for George Dillon, 3.
    - Make a Million, 4.
    - Waiting for Godot, 5.
    - Where's Charley?, 6.
    - The Gazebo, 7.
    - Tevya and His Daughters, 8.
    - Midsummer Night's Dream, 9.
    - Sailor Beware, 10.
    - Open Season, 11.
    - Romanoff and Juliet, 12.
  - 1960-1961 (Box 119, Folder 11-13)
    - Dark at the Top of the Stairs, 1.
    - Golden Fleecing, 2.
    - Silent Night, Lonely Night, 3.
    - Cheating at Love, 4.
    - Legend of Harlequin, 5.
    - Hamlet, 6.
    - Leave It To Jane, 7.
    - The Adventures of the Puppet Prince, 8.
    - The Frog Princess and the Witch, 9.
    - Marriage-Go-Round, 10.
    - Between Two Thieves, 11.
    - Two for the Seesaw, 12.
    - Babes in Arms, 13.
    - Tartuffe, 14.
    - Roar Like a Dove, 15.
    - Send Me No Flowers, 16.
  - 1961-1962 (Box 119, Folder 14-16)
    - Andersonville Trial, 1.
    - The Desk Set, 2.
    - Under the Yum Yum Tree, 3.
    - Playboy of the Western World, 4.
    - The World of Sholom Aleichem/The Bespoke Overcoat, 5.
    - A Pair of Spectacles, 6.
    - School for Scandal/Four Men - Theatre Outlook of England, 7.
    - Big Fish, Little Fish, 8.
    - The Deadly Game, 9.
    - Period of Adjustment, 10.
    - Nude with Violin, 11.
    - Monique, 12.
    - The Prisoner, 13.
    - Little Mary Sunshine, 14.
    - Macbeth, 15.
    - Three Penny Opera, 16.
    - The American Dream and the Zoo Story, 17.
    - South Pacific, 18.
    - The Pleasure of His Company, 19.
    - The Emperor's New Clothes, 20.
    - Cinderella, 21.
    - Beauty and the Beast, 22.
    - Pied Piper of Hamlin, 23.
  - 1962-1963 (Box 119, Folder 17-19)
    - Who'll Save the Ploughboy?, 1.
    - Write Me a Murder, 2.
    - Oh, Kay!, 3.
    - Critic's Choice, 4.
    - The Fantasticks, 5.
    - Fifth Season, 6.
    - Bye Bye Birdie, 7.
    - First Night, 8.
    - Come Blow Your Horn, 9.
    - The Caretaker, 10.
    - Make a Note of It, 11.
    - Anna Kleiber, 12.
    - Taming of the Shrew, 13.
    - Hansel and Gretel, 14.
  - 1963-1964 (Box 120, Folder 1-3)
    - West Side Story, 1.
    - Sunday in New York, 2.
    - Do You Know the Milky Way?, 3.
    - Take Her, She's Mine, 4.
    - Oh, Dad, Poor Dad, Mama's Hung You..., 5.
    - Wish You Were, 6.
    - Tenth Man, 7.
    - Calculated Risk, 8.
    - Twelfth Night, 9.
    - Enter Laughing, 10.
    - The Sinner and the Saint, 11.
    - Naughty Nifties, 12.
  - 1964-1965 (Box 120, Folder 4-6)
    - Thousand Clowns, 1.
    - She Loves Me, 2.
    - The Inspector General, 3.
    - The Firebugs, 4.
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, 5.
    - The Glass Menagerie, 6.
    - The Great Sebastians, 7.
    - Mary, Mary, 8.
    - The Playhouse Follies, 9.
    - The Private Ear and The Public Eye, 10.
  - 1965 (Box 120, Folder 7-8)
    - American Conservatory Theatre, 1.
    - Tartuffe, 2.
    - Tiny Alice, 3.
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 4.
    - Antigone, 5.
    - Rose Tattoo, 6.
    - Noah, 7.
    - American Conservatory Theatre, 8.
    - Apollo of Bellac, 9.
    - King Lear, 10.
    - Servant of Two Masters, 11.
    - In White America, 12.
    - The Devil's Disciple, 13.
    - Death of a Salesman, 14.
    - Beyond the Fringe, 15.
  - 1966 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - The Typists and The Tiger, 1.
    - The Knack, 2.
    - The Mad Show, 3.
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, 4.
    - Rhinoceros, 5.
    - The Complaisant Lover, 6.
  - 1966-1967 (Box 120, Folder 10-11)
    - A Man's A Man, 1.
    - Streetcar Named Desire, 2.
    - The Entertainer, 3.
    - Memory of Two Mondays / A View From the Bridge, 4.
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 5.
    - The Three Sisters, 6.
    - The Fantasticks, 7.
    - Barefoot in the Park, 8.
    - A Hole in the Head, 9.
    - Blue Denim, 10.
  - 1967-1968 (Box 120, Folder 12-14)
    - Once Upon a Mattress, 1.
    - The Tavern, 2.
    - After the Fall, 3.
    - Henry IV, Part I, 4.
    - Rapunzel and the Witch, 5.
    - Born Yesterday, 6.
    - Arms and the Man, 7.
    - Rashomon, 8.
    - The Subject Was Roses, 9.
    - Three Men on a Horse, 10.
    - A Delicate Balance, 11.
    - The Odd Couple, 12.
    - Galileo, 13.
    - Noir et Blanc Mosaic Ballet, 14.
  - 1968-1969 (Box 120, Folder 15-16)
    - Odd Couple, 1.
    - The Little Foxes, 2.
    - Generation, 3.
    - Wait Until Dark, 4.
    - Eight Revue Sketches / The Lover / A Slight Ache, 5.
    - King and I, 6.
    - Jack, Or the Submission / The New Tenant / The Chairs, 7.
    - Act Without Words II / Krapp's Last Tape/ Happy Days, 8.
    - Dear Me, The Sky Is Falling, 9.
    - Aladdin, 10.
    - Mystery at the Old Fort, 11.
    - Rumplestiltskin, 12.
  - 1969-1970 (Box 120, Folder 17-18)
    - Cindy, 1.
    - Hay Fever, 2.
    - Gypsy, 3.
    - The Owl and the Pussycat, 4.
    - The Serpent, 5.
    - Loot, 6.
    - Mystery at Crooked Pine Ranch, 7.
    - The Nutcracker, 8.
    - Dracula, 9.
    - Streets of New York, 10.
    - In White America, 11.
    - Pittsburgh Ballet Theater, 12.
    - Star Spangled Girl, 13.
  - 1970-1971 (Box 121A, Folder 1-2)
    - Your Own Thing, 1.
    - Everything in the Garden, 2.
    - Room Service, 3.
    - No Strings, 4.
    - Luv, 5.
    - Guys Dolls, 6.
    - Catch Me If You Can, 7.
    - Red Juice, 8.
    - The Hostage, 9.
  - 1971-1972 (Box 121A, Folder 3)
    - The Boys in the Band, 1.
    - Anything Goes, 2.
    - Blithe Spirit, 3.
    - The Birthday Party, 4.
    - Plaza Suite / Lion in Winter, 5.
    - Play it Again, Sam, 6.
    - Cactus Flower, 7.
    - Never Too Late, 8.
    - Man of LaMancha, 9.
    - Amahl and the Night Visitors, 10.
    - The Brave Little Tailor, 11.
  - 1972-1973 (Box 121A, Folder 4)
    - Fiddler on the Roof, 1.
    - How the Other Half Loves / Enter a Free Man, 2.
    - Last of the Red Hot Lovers, 3.
    - Forty Carats, 4.
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, 5.
    - You Can't Take It With You, 6.
    - Streetcar Named Desire / Alfred the Great, 7.
    - The Prime of Miss Jean Brodie, 8.
    - Carousel, 9.
    - The Seagull, 10.
    - Salvation, 11.
    - Rapunzel and the Witch, 12.
    - Coppelia, 13.
    - Goldilocks and the Three Bears, 14.
  - 1973-1974 (Box 121A, Folder 5)
    - The Crucible, 1.
    - 3 One-Act Plays for Television, 2.
    - Tom Paine, 3.
    - The Tiger, 4.
    - Next/Adaptation/Sing to Me Through Open Windows, 5.
    - Hello Dolly!, 6.
    - Androcles and the Lion, 7.
    - Ghost of Mr. Penny, 8.
    - Rumplestiltskin, 9.
  - 1974-1975 (Box 121A, Folder 5a)
    - The Indian Captive, 1.
  - 1975-1976 (Box 121A, Folder 6)
    - The Interview, 1.
    - Bus Stop, 2.
  - 1976-1977 (Box 121A, Folder 7)
    - Tartuffe, 1.
  - 1977-1978 (Box 121A, Folder 8)
    - The Hot L Baltimore, 1.
    - A Christmas Carol, 2.
    - Playboy of the Western World, 3.
    - A Night of One Acts, 4.
    - Premiere Performance Point Park Dance Company, 5.
  - 1978-1979 (Box 121A, Folder 9)
    - The Ghost of Mr. Penny, 1.
    - Our Town, 2.
    - Private Lives, 3.
  - 1979-1980 (Box 121A, Folder 10)
    - Nutcracker - American Dance Ensemble, 1.
    - An Evening with Stravinsky and Bernstein - American Dance Ensemble, 2.
    - Rod McKuen in The Dance, Part II - American Dance Ensemble, 3.
    - A History of American Film, 4.
    - A Tribute to Gershwin - American Dance Ensemble, 5.
    - Absent Friends, 6.
    - Clarence Darrow, 7.
    - The Shadow Box, 8.
    - A Life on the Theater, 9.
  - 1980-1981 (Box 121A, Folder 11)
    - Rite of Spring - American Dance Ensemble, 1.
    - Graduation Ball - American Dance Ensemble, 2.
    - Rod McKuen in The Dance, Part III/Benny Goodman, 3.
    - "Let's Swing!" - American Dance Ensemble, 4.
    - Nutcracker - American Dance Ensemble, 5.
    - The Rivals, 6.
    - Twelfth Night, 7.
    - That Championship Season, 8.
    - Deathtrap, 9.
    - Side by Side By Sondheim, 10.
  - 1981-1982 (Box 121A, Folder 12)
    - Lion in Winter, 1.
    - The Vampire Play, 2.
    - Nutcracker, 3.
    - Carmen - American Dance Ensemble, 4.
    - Scheherazade - American Dance Ensemble, 5.
    - Cinderella - American Dance Ensemble, 6.
    - Dames at Sea, 7.
    - Talley's Folley, 8.
    - Romantic Comedy, 9.
    - 1989-1990 (Box 121A, Folder 20)
      - The Emperor's Nightingale, 1.
      - Waiting for Godot, 2.
      - Playboy of the Western World, 3.
      - Becoming Memories, 4.
      - Three Penny Opera, 5.
      - Mystery of Edwin Drood, 6.
      - Walk in the Woods, 7.
      - Dreamgirls, 8.
  - 1982-1983 (Box 121A, Folder 13)
    - Without Apologies, 1.
    - Whose Life Is It Anyway?, 2.
    - Bedroom Farce, 3.
    - Cabaret, 4.
    - Carmina Burana, Minotaur Bolero, 5.
  - 1983-1984 (Box 121A, Folder 14)
    - Something Afoot, 1.
    - American Buffalo, 2.
    - Brave Little Tailor, 3.
  - 1984-1985 (Box 121A, Folder 15)
    - Animal Farm, 1.
    - Rumpelstiltskin, 2.
    - A Christmas Carol, 3.
    - A Little Night Music, 4.
    - Beyond Therapy, 5.
    - Jesus Christ Superstar, 6.
  - 1985-1986 (Box 121A, Folder 16)
    - Godspell, 1.
    - A Chorus Line, 2.
    - Little Shop of Horrors, 3.
    - The Magic Horn, 4.
    - Two Gentlemen of Verona, 5.
    - Philadelphia Here I Come, 6.
    - Cinderella, 7.
    - Little Red Riding Hood, 8.
    - Marat/Sade, 9.
    - The Indian Captive, 10.
  - 1986-1987 (Box 121A, Folder 17)
    - The Servant of Two Masters, 1.
    - Working: A Musical, 2.
    - Getting Out, 3.
    - Little Shop of Horrors, 4.
    - 1940's Radio Hour, 5.
    - Brighton Beach Memoirs, 6.
    - Peter Pan, 7.
  - 1987-1988 (Box 121A, Folder 18)
    - Tartuffe, 1.
    - Hamlet, 2.
    - Evita, 3.
    - 42nd Street, 4.
    - You Can't Take It With You, 5.
  - 1988-1989 (Box 121A, Folder 19)
    - The Hostage, 1.
    - The Day Room, 2.
    - Anything Goes, 3.
    - Time of Your Life, 4.
    - Chicago, 5.
  - 1990-1991 (Box 121B, Folder 1)
    - Merlin and Arthur, 1.
    - La Cage aux Folles, 2.
    - the Playboy of the Western World, 3.
    - the Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe, 4.
    - the Emperor's Nightingale, 5.
    - Steel Magnolias, 6.
    - Little Red Riding Hood, 7.
    - 2 by 5, 8.
    - Savage in Limbo and Welcome to the Moon, 9.
    - Becoming Memories, 10.
    - Puss in Boots, 11.
    - Leader of the Pack, 12.
    - Winnie the Pooh, 13.
    - Aladdin, 14.
    - Treasure Island, 15.
  - 1991-1992 (Box 121B, Folder 2)
    - Legend of Sleepy Hollow, 1.
    - Me and My Girl, 2.
    - Amadeus, 3.
    - Beauty and the Beast, 4.
    - Noises Off, 5.
    - the Fantasticks, 6.
    - the Secret Garden, 7.
    - Top Girls, 8.
    - Big River, 9.
    - Velveteen Rabbit, 10.
    - Tom Sawyer, 11.
    - An Evening with Shirley Jones, 12.
  - 1992-1993 (Box 121B, Folder 3)
    - the Canterville Ghost, 1.
    - Dames at Sea, 2.
    - Snow White and Rose Red, 3.
    - What the Butler Saw, 4.
    - Robber Bridegroom, 5.
    - Jack and the Beantree, 6.
    - Blue Window, 7.
    - Pippin, 8.
    - Ugly Duckling, 9.
    - the Three Musketeers, 10.
  - 1993-1994 (Box 121B, Folder 4)
    - the Good Woman of Setzuan, 1.
    - Oklahoma, 2.
    - Rapunzel, 3.
    - Company, 4.
    - Hair, 5.
    - Emperor's New Clothes, 6.
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 7.
    - Jungle Book, 8.
    - Charlotte's Web, 9.
    - Driving Miss Daisy, 10.
- Pressbooks, Clippings, Brochures and Press Releases, 1934-1994; V.
  Newspaper clippings and articles bound in pressbooks and scrapbooks and photocopied single articles concerned with the Playhouse, its productions, members, students, and social activities as well as publicity material disseminated by the Playhouse administration to attract subscribers, students, etc. The scrapbooks also contain compilations of articles on other community theater activities of the 1930s such as Pittsburgh Civic Playhouse, Fort Pitt Hotel, Pittsburgh Little Theater, and Pittsburgh Summer Playhouse.
  - Press Books, 1934-1974; 1.
    Compilation of the volumes in this subseries was done commercially through a clippings service. These volumes have been disbound so the contents could be mircofilmed. Several of the earliest press books were also preservation photocopied into bound volumes. Except in these instances, it is recommended that researchers use the microfilm copies.
    - 1934-1935 (Box 121B, Volume 1)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 121B, Volume 2)
    - 1937-1940 (Box 121B, Volume 3)
    - 1940-1943 (Box 121B, Volume 4)
    - 1943-1945 (Box 121B, Volume 5)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 121B, Volume 6)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 121B, Volume 7)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 121B, Volume 8)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 121B, Volume 9)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 121B, Volume 10)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 121B, Volume 11)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 121B, Volume 12)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 121B, Volume 13)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 121B, Volume 14)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 121B, Volume 15A)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 121B, Volume 15B)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 121B, Volume 16)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 121B, Volume 17)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 121B, Volume 18)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 121B, Volume 19)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 121B, Volume 20)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 121B, Volume 21)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 121B, Volume 22)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 121B, Volume 23)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 121B, Volume 24)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 121B, Volume 25)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 121B, Volume 26A)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 121B, Volume 26B)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 121B, Volume 26C)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 121B, Volume 27)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 121B, Volume 28)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 121B, Volume 29)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 121B, Volume 30)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 121B, Volume 31)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 121B, Volume 32)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 121B, Volume 33)
  - Scrapbooks, 1933-1953; 2.
    All of these volumes are extremely brittle; please handle with great care. Compiler assumed to be Helen Wayne Rauh.
    - Pittsburgh Playhouse scrapbook, 1946-1953 (Box 121B, Volume 1)
      Programs, brochures, announcements, photos, and clippings from the Playhouse School of the Theater courses and productions of theater and related activities. Also includes early clippings on Shirley Jones as a beauty pageant contestant and actress. Also included are a few programs from the Curtaineers of the Irene Kaufmann Settlement and Children's Civic Theatre Society.
    - Pittsburgh Playhouse scrapbook, 1934-1935 (Box 121B, Volume 2)
      Clippings related to the opening season, 1934-35, of the Pittsburgh Playhouse. The majority of this volume is clippings, programs, announcements, and tickets of the Pittsburgh Civic Playhouse's Summer 1934 Season at the Arnold School. Includes clippings of Judith Anderson's appearance in the premiere of Female of the Species, August 1934.
    - Snatched from the Noose scrapbook, 1936 (Box 121B, Volume 3)
      Clippings, photographs and programs related to the production of the melodrama, Snatched from the Noose, Fort Pitt Hotel, 1936.
    - Pittsburgh Summer Playhouse scrapbook, 1933-1934 (Box 121B, Volume 4)